<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
<document>  
	<properties>  
		<author email="jk AT jkraemer.net">Jens Kraemer</author>
		<title>XWiki Lucene Plugin - Changelog</title>
	</properties>  
	<meta name="keyword" content="xwiki, lucene, plugin"/> 
	<body>
		<section name="Changelog">
			<subsection name="trunk (0.9.3)">
				<ul>
					<li>Fix removing index creation problems on Win32 platforms - Thanks to Daniel Cortes for looking into this</li>
					<li>Fix which removes NPE which only occured when the Log4J log level was not set to debug</li>
				</ul>
			</subsection>
			<subsection name="0.9.2">
				<ul>
					<li>
						Multi language support - Now the content of all translations of documents should get
						indexed on index rebuild, too.
					</li>
					<li>
						the getSearchResults methods now return a SearchResults Object, allowing to retrieve 
						only a subset of the results using getResults(int beginIndex, int resultCount).
						The SearchResults class also enforces the check if the user doing the search has 
						access to a document, before adding it to the list of results.
					</li>
					<li>
					</li>
					<li>
						Several API changes to allow searching virtual wikis, access rights checking and 
						searching for documents of specific languages only. See the Api docs 
						of <a href="/xwiki/lucene-plugin/apidocs/net/jkraemer/xwiki/plugins/lucene/LucenePluginApi.html">LucenePluginApi</a> 
						for more details.
					</li>
					<li>
						Updated <a href="searchForm.vm">searchForm.vm</a> to reflect the paging, virtual 
						wiki and multi language support.
					</li>
				</ul>
			</subsection>
			<subsection name="0.9.1">
				<ul>
					<li>
						Better handling of index rebuilds - until now all document contents have been 
						fetched *before*
						starting to index - bad with huge attachments and big wikis. Now the content of a 
						document or attachment is fetched right before getting indexed.
					</li>
					<li>
            Added some fields:
						<ul><li><pre>lang</pre> containing the language 
						of a document. This fixes the problem that a document version in one language 
						replaced all other language versions of this document when it was indexed.</li>
							<li>creator</li>
							<li>creationDate</li>
						</ul>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed bug which made deletion of old document versions not working.
					</li>
					<li>
						Queries for date ranges now work, just use date:[20040101 TO 20050101] 
						to find all documents modified in 2004
					</li>
					<li>
						Document name, web and author are stored in a way searchable by the user 
						by naming the fields directly: web:main will find all Documents from the 
						'Main' Web
					</li>
					<li>
						updated the search form
					</li>
				</ul>		
			</subsection>
			<subsection name="0.9">
				<p>
					Initial release.
				</p>
			</subsection>
			
		</section>
	</body>
</document>
