<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
<document>  
	<properties>  
		<author email="jk AT jkraemer.net">Jens Kraemer</author>
		<title>XWiki Email Notification Plugin</title>
	</properties>  
	<meta name="keyword" content="xwiki, notification, email, plugin"/> 
	<body>
		<section name="XWiki Email Notification Plugin">
			<subsection name="Get it!">
				<p><a href="../dist/">Download</a> | <a href="install.html">Installation instructions</a> | <a href="http://svn.forge.objectweb.org/cgi-bin/viewcvs.cgi/xwiki/xwiki-plugins/emailnotification/">SVN Repository</a></p>
			</subsection>
			<subsection name="About this plugin">
				<p>
					This plugin allows users of Xwiki to receive notifications about changes of 
          documents by email. 
				</p>
				<p>Features:</p>
				<ul>
<li>Users can subscribe to single documents, webs, or choose to receive notifications for the whole wiki.</li>
<li>Overlapping subscriptions (i.e. whole wiki and some single pages from this wiki subscribed) do not result in double-notifications.</li>
<li>Multiple subsequent modifications to the same document in a single notification interval 
are aggregated and result in the document being shown in the notification mail only once (last change is shown). This could easily be extended to display the complete change history.</li>
<li>Users of course don't get notified of their own changes.</li>
<li>The Administrator of a wiki can decide what notification intervals he wants to offer. 
This is done by simply defining cron-like expressions in a properties file. The user can 
then choose one of these defined intervals.</li>
<li>Users can edit their subscription settings by opening to their home page (XWiki.username) 
with the object editor. Once the user has subscribed his first document there will be an 
instance of class Plugins.EmailSubscriptions attached to this page. This instance 
holds all subscribed pages and webs, and the selected notification interval. This data 
can be directly modified through the object editor.</li>
<li>Notification mails are based on a velocity template which allows easy customization.</li>
				</ul>
			</subsection>
		</section>
	</body>
</document>
